<<<<<<< HEAD
{
	"header": {
		"name": "Topic One"
	},
	"cards": [
		{
			"metadata": {
				"topic": "topic",
				"state": "postgrad",
				"confidence": 250,
				"interval": 345600,
				"last_reviewed": 1638451223,
				"next_review": 1638796823,
				"last_review_indicator": "4"
			},
			"question": "Q1",
			"answer": "A1"
		},
		{
			"metadata": {
				"topic": "topic",
				"state": "postgrad",
				"confidence": 250,
				"interval": 345600,
				"last_reviewed": 1638451498,
				"next_review": 1638797098,
				"last_review_indicator": "4"
			},
			"question": "Q3",
			"answer": "A3"
		},
		{
			"metadata": {
				"topic": "topic",
				"state": "postgrad",
				"confidence": 250,
				"interval": 345600,
				"last_reviewed": 1638451218,
				"next_review": 1638796818,
				"last_review_indicator": "4"
			},
			"question": "Q3",
			"answer": "A3"
		},
		{
			"metadata": {
				"topic": "topic",
				"state": "postgrad",
				"confidence": 250,
				"interval": 345600,
				"last_reviewed": 1638451499,
				"next_review": 1638797099,
				"last_review_indicator": "4"
			},
			"question": "Q2",
			"answer": "A2"
		},
		{
			"metadata": {
				"topic": "topic",
				"state": "postgrad",
				"confidence": 250,
				"interval": 345600,
				"last_reviewed": 1638451221,
				"next_review": 1638796821,
				"last_review_indicator": "4"
			},
			"question": "Q4",
			"answer": "A4"
		},
		{
			"metadata": {
				"topic": "topic",
				"state": "postgrad",
				"confidence": 250,
				"interval": 345600,
				"last_reviewed": 1638451500,
				"next_review": 1638797100,
				"last_review_indicator": "4"
			},
			"question": "Q1",
			"answer": "A1"
		},
		{
			"metadata": {
				"topic": "topic",
				"state": "postgrad",
				"confidence": 250,
				"interval": 345600,
				"last_reviewed": 1638451219,
				"next_review": 1638796819,
				"last_review_indicator": "4"
			},
			"question": "Q2",
			"answer": "A2"
		},
		{
			"metadata": {
				"topic": "topic",
				"state": "postgrad",
				"confidence": 250,
				"interval": 345600,
				"last_reviewed": 1638451502,
				"next_review": 1638797102,
				"last_review_indicator": "4"
			},
			"question": "Q4",
			"answer": "A4"
		}
	]
}F
=======
{"header": {"name": "Topic One"}, "cards": [{"meta_data": {"topic": "topic", "confidence": 200.0, "interval": 60, "last_reviewed": 1638386807, "next_review": 1638386867}, "question": "Q1", "answer": "A1"}, {"meta_data": {"topic": "topic", "confidence": 250, "interval": null, "last_reviewed": null, "next_review": null}, "question": "Q2", "answer": "A2"}, {"meta_data": {"topic": "topic", "confidence": 250, "interval": null, "last_reviewed": null, "next_review": null}, "question": "Q1", "answer": "A1"}, {"meta_data": {"topic": "topic", "confidence": 212.5, "interval": 600, "last_reviewed": 1638386565, "next_review": 1638387165}, "question": "Q4", "answer": "A4"}, {"meta_data": {"topic": "topic", "confidence": 250, "interval": null, "last_reviewed": null, "next_review": null}, "question": "Q2", "answer": "A2"}, {"meta_data": {"topic": "topic", "confidence": 250, "interval": 86400, "last_reviewed": 1638386494, "next_review": 1638472894}, "question": "Q4", "answer": "A4"}, {"meta_data": {"topic": "topic", "confidence": 250, "interval": null, "last_reviewed": null, "next_review": null}, "question": "Q2", "answer": "A2"}, {"meta_data": {"topic": "topic", "confidence": 287.5, "interval": 345600, "last_reviewed": 1638386661, "next_review": 1638732261}, "question": "Q3", "answer": "A3"}, {"meta_data": {"topic": "topic", "confidence": 250, "interval": null, "last_reviewed": null, "next_review": null}, "question": "Q3", "answer": "A3"}, {"meta_data": {"topic": "topic", "confidence": 250, "interval": null, "last_reviewed": null, "next_review": null}, "question": "Q4", "answer": "A4"}, {"meta_data": {"topic": "topic", "confidence": 250, "interval": null, "last_reviewed": null, "next_review": null}, "question": "Q1", "answer": "A1"}, {"meta_data": {"topic": "topic", "confidence": 250, "interval": null, "last_reviewed": null, "next_review": null}, "question": "Q3", "answer": "A3"}]}
>>>>>>> parent of ed55899 (Spaced repatition algorithm testing.)
